{
    "subject": "resource/Gladys_Knight_&_the_Pips",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Gladys Knight & the Pips is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8891398906707764,
            "question": "Where are Gladys Knight & the Pips from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7869715690612793,
            "question": "What country is Gladys Knight & the Pips associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.632824182510376,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations involving Gladys Knight & the Pips?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6146056056022644,
            "question": "Is Gladys Knight & the Pips a musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.522367000579834,
            "question": "What genre of music is Gladys Knight & the Pips known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5204862356185913,
            "question": "During what era were Gladys Knight & the Pips most popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4866331219673157,
            "question": "Has Gladys Knight & the Pips won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4739763140678406,
            "question": "What impact have Gladys Knight & the Pips had on music history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44802162051200867,
            "question": "What is the name of the lead singer in Gladys Knight & the Pips?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38999685645103455,
            "question": "Can you name any popular songs by Gladys Knight & the Pips?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gladys Knight & the Pips is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_505_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the lead singer in Gladys Knight & the Pips?",
            "html": "dbpedia_505_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact have Gladys Knight & the Pips had on music history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_505_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Gladys Knight & the Pips won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_505_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_505_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's my evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Gladys Knight & the Pips were an American R&B/soul group, formed in Atlanta, Georgia in 1953. This suggests that they are from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Gladys Knight and The Pips were an American R&B/soul group formed in Atlanta, Georgia, which confirms that they are from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Gladys Knight & the Pips is an American group, thus it originates from the United States.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states they were formed in Atlanta, Georgia.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The information provided directly states that Gladys Knight And The Pips were an \"American R&B/soul group\" which implies they are from the United States.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly states that Gladys Knight And The Pips were an American R&B/soul group formed in Atlanta, Georgia. Therefore, they are from the United States.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}